[
  {
    "question": "1x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3672cfec-dea7-427b-8d8b-a75100863491"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x1",
    "answer": "1",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "353c6441-3fd4-4a05-9f82-754de0cba5ac"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x2",
    "answer": "2",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3d486920-4fa2-4cab-af4f-9d27b1644991"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x3",
    "answer": "3",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6523f273-8f5a-4242-8279-b02ddd12b049"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x4",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fe5aa281-de01-48a8-8b7a-eeaaedafbb2f"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x5",
    "answer": "5",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "69bfa6da-e8ae-45c4-8206-10e509bd9c87"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x6",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a09a3680-5080-4e38-b4ee-5f958bbfd996"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x7",
    "answer": "7",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "03ecb177-1bd3-4f35-b328-0b47f8505a90"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x8",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e065fc88-ab31-4163-b11e-6fd0242d68e7"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x9",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a5b3b80d-5342-4750-9ba6-5e3a0287daa5"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x10",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "01a81e2a-00d7-4f6a-9389-b98b55b5a9e6"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0591966b-49c2-4cd5-8ce0-ca959406e785"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x1",
    "answer": "2",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "deda0c9a-bbba-40ef-be64-1b7ec1631d03"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x2",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "dff30539-2a70-48e0-aa4a-6b93223dc383"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x3",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "df44308e-77cc-4bb6-bd16-99e5a34ae1f9"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x4",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "19934678-4731-479d-b9f1-c38334a7da60"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x5",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "57994724-931b-4b37-ab70-74c0edf343f4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x6",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d783d287-3b7f-42e1-aa23-2e50b9980498"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x7",
    "answer": "14",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d2ae5883-a34d-451c-8adb-6c18eb3d420a"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x8",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "7cc13349-73ec-4571-81f7-d2323de848f1"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x9",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "67b7b9f1-65b9-4525-ba05-0cd71a0ad56b"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x10",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9e54bc4d-09d7-4bbb-aa9f-0814fbb3f950"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "856d8b37-ebd6-471e-9179-0d2cdf09bcd0"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x1",
    "answer": "3",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "37849a70-e173-4829-96bc-5c108f3644bc"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x2",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "08b443b8-4e10-4f14-90a6-6083b7c02d4c"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x3",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5161a752-f9fe-4ab8-90c8-dc3c47f3deb3"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x4",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5ba920b6-caa7-49f0-aeec-55fb8b845cf3"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x5",
    "answer": "15",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "21dd4521-e490-42ad-92af-1d21b0909b7e"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x6",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "410c0d38-3a58-4c4b-a6f5-b2e1ef392bc1"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x7",
    "answer": "21",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "be3b3f62-9f3b-4a41-9d4a-3242aaff047c"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x8",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0e61d83d-c8a6-4172-88ad-fa0d38c6d7e2"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x9",
    "answer": "27",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8b0e705f-5e8b-47ac-b8a1-caed19dfe134"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x10",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3313bef7-0e2c-4aa6-8263-8399d441fef5"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a54eb2f0-4a88-4837-9206-814d715496ba"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x1",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3fb38b9b-45ad-4ae6-8c6f-3e94c2df4ed5"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x2",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3d579dd7-b35d-4a28-bb41-2ccef9c4a93a"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x3",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "67a61e8f-920a-45f4-a718-3bb71ab6f172"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x4",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1501a7de-1cd2-43e3-bc62-52b623374899"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x5",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "f7fa4351-f3d6-472d-896d-d0434f58844a"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x6",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a26f3281-24a1-442f-a9bc-3b0994135ea7"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x7",
    "answer": "28",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3dac79f4-9e7e-4ce7-ae78-1444fff8c1e7"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x8",
    "answer": "32",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3d20f454-7ec1-4b9c-9a7c-9d151ac196b3"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x9",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e76a2c33-1121-4e1e-b4c4-376213fff64c"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x10",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fd239500-9103-442e-92ab-d4c063c16dd4"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a16edb0a-4216-4f19-8026-c1cb4a165f94"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x1",
    "answer": "5",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6931bcad-1b27-48ae-86ee-2d1ad33429ad"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x2",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "f1710482-2d2a-4a7c-aa28-618d15e14a39"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x3",
    "answer": "15",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "546a0ec2-76e4-4e5f-ab4b-3f83e920ae4d"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x4",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "91839deb-c9c1-491f-a600-50fe48081933"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x5",
    "answer": "25",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "b8f7641a-9915-49c3-aa25-717ebaba125f"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x6",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0c11e9fb-fc73-4ca8-9aef-583f9437be6e"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x7",
    "answer": "35",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "2483460e-97a1-4f29-b4fb-f0511da070e4"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x8",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "57eeea66-34d4-4d03-94ce-d4ed3b66ae22"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x9",
    "answer": "45",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8caa23cd-b50b-4dd0-9eb9-2b91a4008eb9"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x10",
    "answer": "50",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a1265735-8977-4e2b-a929-b68ed34134ae"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "039aee16-d585-4a27-acc8-3b0319e796fb"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x1",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "957118dc-872f-4d55-ac50-de0369aae7be"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x2",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4372fa89-991f-4d3c-9ea1-a0847659064d"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x3",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a686121a-0902-4b87-8de4-b724f4dc4f37"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x4",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "171370a9-942c-4ffb-98ce-bfe24bb51665"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x5",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "7c4534db-6ef1-441b-9e32-9cbf7501083b"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x6",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0087c36d-e385-434f-b9af-e02ec3fdc983"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x7",
    "answer": "42",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1fd6d332-f87d-4ecc-9d5e-c350a508a942"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x8",
    "answer": "48",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "2962b618-a187-4ae0-b9a5-283f02c841cb"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x9",
    "answer": "54",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ac08328f-2f36-498d-9818-9cac0cb7173f"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x10",
    "answer": "60",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ab2a9e29-cc02-4552-9709-1712879d7791"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e6fe861a-22b2-4616-a1ab-aab548d3c518"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x1",
    "answer": "7",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "06ed37f4-7d20-4f87-b8cf-3c6ff820cace"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x2",
    "answer": "14",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5db4d2c4-d553-4d05-85ee-c349a8b1fee7"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x3",
    "answer": "21",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "bd29cfcb-a0ac-4bcb-89c1-f624327074d6"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x4",
    "answer": "28",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "afc5fc95-971d-47cf-82b2-78fd8e7f388e"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x5",
    "answer": "35",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "87394f12-1caf-46fa-be50-ee253f59b0de"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x6",
    "answer": "42",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "791d5b6c-2340-4352-8a6d-a6191b973b0d"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x7",
    "answer": "49",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5111db9c-d065-4374-9d96-ff604f6a13c2"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x8",
    "answer": "56",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e6727b05-ae46-4a79-96fc-4e5d25d05524"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x9",
    "answer": "63",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "c177ae0a-73c1-4fa4-807a-9d36037045ea"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x10",
    "answer": "70",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "981b5660-a41b-485e-a57b-89ada6991972"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3eb8701c-a1e5-4852-806c-bca2d86150f3"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x1",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "24ef5190-39f7-41f7-a0db-1ab7f1d4d10c"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x2",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e96b8812-70fc-4666-ba07-ceaf3f24664d"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x3",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "48de32f2-46ab-4603-87ff-fbdb5fa6d4bd"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x4",
    "answer": "32",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "018f8505-226d-4bba-ae71-ed58e011e009"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x5",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "82c4df4f-ec72-4774-9fed-2fb29412d738"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x6",
    "answer": "48",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "833e3840-f6a0-49d5-b795-0b3427685fd6"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x7",
    "answer": "56",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d1f2de39-ccc6-4b07-8872-8342e47e1382"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x8",
    "answer": "64",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "25e88e78-88ff-4086-bbbf-45a15e347138"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x9",
    "answer": "72",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "62159ad4-0c4b-4389-be3a-898c49a604da"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x10",
    "answer": "80",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8f292ace-a200-4ffe-92e3-e2f0d21bfc94"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1ebd8270-09fb-48b8-ad98-a13d420cc43e"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x1",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "de368a32-f986-4f8b-b3c3-201d98efd09a"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x2",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "17d471a0-370b-4b58-8e00-1abb722f0ce6"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x3",
    "answer": "27",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "690eb717-cb18-4a84-9cdb-f7f008ad9b0a"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x4",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "303addf9-10e5-4be9-953d-fb6e5d304be6"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x5",
    "answer": "45",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ee019c19-9e6d-449c-a2ef-45d5399153ab"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x6",
    "answer": "54",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "454910cd-c52f-471a-a711-707106c64420"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x7",
    "answer": "63",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "275bbad0-7beb-4901-8b14-76ecc2b50536"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x8",
    "answer": "72",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4185b1b3-cc41-4b10-b55e-76fe11144b32"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x9",
    "answer": "81",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e9df3007-f5c7-4aef-85ab-3a69153da3e2"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x10",
    "answer": "90",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3e6e521e-1d82-451d-aba9-1f10b65f0ab4"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "b6aab162-d88a-45a2-8fb8-7d0af052af09"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x1",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "92259cb5-13d3-42c6-86ed-90a3f80c0cfb"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x2",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8e0b694f-486d-4ab0-afe4-988ccd61661a"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x3",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "905111af-dc08-41ae-bf17-87464e75c6ff"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x4",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6029427f-e38d-4423-b0bb-9f31f24ac5d8"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x5",
    "answer": "50",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "2f0eaf8e-8b39-4c1e-8b5a-4fe4c2bbed82"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x6",
    "answer": "60",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "82bf7d21-ccc1-4145-b312-7e87f6555ae6"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x7",
    "answer": "70",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "80ee3182-5822-48e8-84d0-24aecaeab502"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x8",
    "answer": "80",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "c539b33e-7239-408b-8a54-a8abd2c38e4f"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x9",
    "answer": "90",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5a2bd4a5-4f2d-406f-8bca-0bb52b9b679b"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x10",
    "answer": "100",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6536605f-2c6f-41a1-bc08-dd4b1aeb1e9b"
  }
]